expressionCalc Info since Feb 11th 2011
Started Date : Jan 07th 2011
Project Completed : Feb 25th 2011

~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
The JCreator project of expressionCalc was abandoned
Futher developments have been continue with NetBeans IDE
I get successful start with JCreator and basic calculations are
exactly correct according to our testing
I hope to add more mathematical functions such as Sin, Cos,
Tan, Log, Pow etc.
Feb 11th 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
Bug Summery
According to Testing I found some bug types
1.When gave -- or -+ or -+-+---+
2.The broblem of brackets
  -If no. of openning brackets not equals to no. of closing brackets
   It gave wrong answer without showing any error
  -When gave (5*9)2 then cloasing bracket not consider as a multiplication
Feb 12th 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
Developments Started

Solve the problem of (5*9)2
Now that expression consider as a (5*9)*2

Today I start to develop VisC# project of expressionCalc parallely to
Java Project
And I add more mathematical operators, Now expressionCalc can solve
	5%2=1
	2^3=8
	e=2.78... these expressions
It now consider % (modulas) ^ (power) and e
Feb 13th 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
Add New functions
nPr	nCr	!(factorial)	pi=3.14...

As a result of lots of hard works during passed days, I could add these
functions to expressionCalc

Now expressionCalc follow some standards
For nPr and nCr you can give only capital P and C
For pi and e you can give only simple pi and e

There is a problem of factorial, nPr and nCr
When we give 10-5!, that subtraction sign consider as minus sign
If you want to do that calculation you should give 10-(5!)

Still, I couldn't solve Feb 12th (1) & (2) problems
Feb 18th 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
Today I try to add Math functions
And I use exMath to solve functions. This code I wrote Feb 19th
It can use as a user difined library class

I change the execution method of expressionCalc. Add Main class
Now expressionCalc class work as a user defined library class
Anyone can use it, for their own works
Now there are two library classes in this project

I checked performances of expressionCalc
It takes at around 0.13 mili second to solve mathematical expression
And solving speed is 7400expressions per second

I have no doubt about performance. The only thing is thinking the way of
capture functions and how to solve

Feb 22nd 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________

12:17PM Feb 23rd 2011 My dream becomes true...........

I did it... Yeh!!! I made the expressionCal with all functionalities
I achive! I found the way to capture functions. Now it's working...
:-)

Feb 23rd 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
Main Developments of expressionCalc are finished
Testing and Maintenance will have to be done

There is one function still not finished. It is log(base,no)
If I couldn't compleate it before Feb 28th, I'll remove it
Because it is not necessary.

I decided to release the expression calculator on Feb 28th
Without any bug, and it is be the first complete version
I finished Visual C# project also

Now all projects are ready to final testings
Thanks for all, who supported me even a word to build this calculator

Feb 23rd 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
OK, I add log() function successfully!
Now coding is finished.

PS : I add abs() function (absolute value)
I try to add || mark for absoulute value like in Math
but it is too hard to check opening and closing marks
because both marks are same
Any way I add abs()

And I make icon for expressionCalc Now it's time to draw GUI

Feb 24th 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
12:02AM Feb 25th 2011

I wanted to completed all works of expressionCalc before Feb 24th
I did it, but 2minuts passed I thought why my calender shows
today is Feb 25th
Becacuse time is 12:02AM The new day is began

Anyway I want to say, I completed all works
	Solve ++, -+- problem
	Solve less no of brackets informing problem
	Solve log(no) whithout base or no problem
	Solve simple c for nCr problem

And add good and formal GUI design
Everything completed, Now I proudly present you the expressionCalc 1.1.1

Use it, you feel easy...

Feb 25th 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
________________________________________________________________________
2:50PM Feb 25th 2011

This is the last set of words which I add into this bio file
Documentaion is comlpeted
Executable applications are redy
Luanching Pack is redy to release

You can use expressionCalc 1.1.1 Feb 28th 2011

Feb 25th 2011 - අමිත් චින්තක
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~